mypuzzle.org 2018-01-31

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**

Mypuzzle.org is committed to protecting your privacy online. Mypuzzle.org does not collect any personal information.

**IP address and logging**

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

**Third Party Advertising**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Liability**

It is Mypuzzle.org's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, Mypuzzle.org will immediately disable and remove games in question.

**External Links**

Mypuzzle.org site contains links to other sites. Mypuzzle.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
